(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.1",
"generated_at": "2026-07-31T18:24:53.357244",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
ow !
Ow!
huh
come chase me
everyday i spent crying ’ bout
Everyday I spent crying 'bout
almost-loves turned complicated
on the way yah
on the way, yeah.
my heart got torn up, shredded, all but dead and
My heart got torn up, shredded, all but dead,
now they say i
now they say I—
i’m just a masochist, they’re sick of it
I'm just a masochist, they're sick of it.
boy take a hint
you ain’t gon’ ever get this
you ain't gon' ever get this!
pedal to the metal, shootin’ straight to the stars
Pedal to the metal, shootin' straight to the stars,
got a craving, like the danger on me
( yeah she like it like that, like that )
(Yeah, she like it like that, like that!)
up another level
temptation you just can’t deny
temptation you just can't deny.
come get a taste but can’t say i won’t bite
Come get a taste, but can't say I won't bite!
supersonic, i’m heading out, i’m gonna
Supersonic, I'm heading out, I'm gonna—
ahh
in my eyes, nirvana
pushing for the high, my lover, i gotta
Pushing for the high, my lover, I gotta—
run
but it’s fun to see you try
But it's fun to see you try.
so hit me up !
So hit me up!
off the map i’mma take it, all my energy
Off the map, I'mma take it, all my energy!
speedin’ up fast
Speedin' up fast,
ready, target locked
hit the dash, i’m upgraded and you want a piece
Hit the dash, I'm upgraded and you want a piece.
so hit me up !
So hit me up!
so hit me up, ah
i never stop
in a new territory
i’m on the edge of glory
I'm on the edge of glory!
boy just watch how i move
gimme that rush
got no regrets in my mind
boy, it’s on you this time
Boy, it's on you this time!
so hit me up
outta luck, volume up, you got a crush ?
Outta luck, volume up, you got a crush?
such a cliché, your bad boy charms, thought i’d fall right back in your arms
Such a cliché, your bad boy charms, thought I'd fall right back in your arms.
wasn’t enough, you needed more, now you’re begging to let you score
Wasn't enough, you needed more, now you're begging to let you score.
surely you’ll take it all in stride, i’mma be busy tonight
Surely you'll take it all in stride, I'mma be busy tonight!
goodbye, goodbye, gotta leave you dry
always try’na play it cool, 20/20 vision on me
Always try'na play it cool, 20/20 vision on me.
just outside my field of view
( yeah she like it like that, like that )
(Yeah, she like it like that, like that!)
engine booming, that’s my cue
Engine booming, that's my cue!
catch me if you can, you better keep up the chase
boy you’re falling behind
boy, you're falling behind.
supersonic, i’m heading out, i’m gonna
Supersonic, I'm heading out, I'm gonna—
ahh
in my eyes, nirvana
pushing for the high, my lover, i gotta
Pushing for the high, my lover, I gotta—
run
but it’s fun to see you try
But it's fun to see you try.
so hit me up !
So hit me up!
off the map i’mma take it, all my energy
Off the map, I'mma take it, all my energy!
speedin’ up fast
Speedin' up fast,
ready, target locked
hit the dash, i’’m upgraded and you want a piece
Hit the dash, I'm upgraded and you want a piece.
so hit me up !
So hit me up!
so hit me up, ah
i never stop
in a new territory
i’’m on the edge of glory
I'm on the edge of glory!
( boy just watch how i move )
(Boy, just watch how I move!)
ow!
huh
come chase me
everyday i spent crying 'bout almost-loves turned complicated
Every day I spent crying 'bout almost-loves turned complicated
on the way yah
on the way, yeah.
my heart got torn up, shredded, all but dead and
now they say i
i'm just a masochist, they're sick of it
now they say I'm just a masochist, they're sick of it.
boy take a hint
you ain't gon' ever get this
pedal to the metal shootin' straight to the stars
got a cravin', like the danger on me
(yeah she like it like that, like that)
up another level
temptation you just can't deny
come get a taste but can't say i won't bite
supersonic, i'm heading out, i'm gonna (ahh)
Supersonic, I'm heading out, I'm gonna— (ah)
in my eyes, nirvana (oh i'm taking off now!)
pushing for the high, my lover, i gotta (run)
but it's fun to see you try
(so hit me up!)
off the map i'mma take it, all my energy
Off the map, I'ma take it, all my energy.
(so hit me up!)
speedin' up fast
(So hit me up!) Speedin' up fast,
ready, target locked
(so hit me up!)
hit the dash, i'm upgraded and you want a piece
(So hit me up!) Hit the dash, I'm upgraded and you want a piece.
(so hit me up!)
so hit me up, ah
(So hit me up!) So hit me up, ah,
i never stop
in a new territory
i'm on the edge of glory
(boy just watch how i move)
gimme that rush
got no regrets in my mind
boy, it's on you this time
so hit me up
outta luck, volume up
So hit me up, outta luck, volume up.
you got a crush?
such a cliché, your bad boy charms
thought i'd fall right back in your arms
wasn't enough, you needed more
now you're begging to let you score
surely you'll take it all in stride
i'mma be busy tonight
Yay! キキリキ! Welcome to my birthday in 2025!
Yay! Kikiriki! Welcome to my birthday in 2025!
Woohoo! お誕生日です! 私の何と何と...何歳になってるんでしょう、この不死鳥?
Woohoo! It's my birthday! How old am I turning this time, this phoenix?
It is my birthday. It is a very special occasion. It is not just my birthday, it is also the Super Special Summer! We will make it a super special summer today, yes, yes.
And if you guys want, I have a hashtag up here, so please make use of it. It is #KiaraBDay2025. So post it all over social media!
Screenshots, or gifts, or GIFs, whatever you want, share it to the world, spread the wawa love! Thank you already in advance.
We started, little, her song with Kiara's Hit Me Up, another banger from my good friend Kira. Thank you for providing the world with bangers. I'm taking them for myself. Hehehe, they're mine now.
We started our song with Kiara's 'Hit Me Up', another banger from my good friend KIRA. Thank you for providing the world with bangers. I'm taking them for myself. Hehehe, they're mine now.
Yeah, that was fun! And did you like the little spicy dance? Hehehe.
And let's take a little look at the stage. ステージを観ましょうか！Well, besides the Super Special Summer logo, we have some presents.
And let's take a little look at the stage. Shall we look at the stage? Well, besides the Super Special Summer logo, we have some presents.
I wonder what's inside. And some balloons, maybe I'm gonna pop them when I'm done here! Hehehe. Yes! And then besides that, today, you know, why is it, why it's so special?
Well, because we're going to have super special merch at the end! We're going to have super special outside guest! Ah! I never had an outside guest before! Exciting! And, and, and, super special song reveal? Hmm, yeah, yeah, probably. You know me.
Well, because we're going to have super special merch at the end! We're going to have a super special outside guest! Ah! I've never had an outside guest before! Exciting! And, and, and, a super special song reveal? Hmm, yeah, yeah, probably. You know me.
So, please watch until the very end! 最後まで見てください！特別なサプライズ一杯ありますからね！よろしくお願いします！
So, please watch until the very end! Please watch until the end! There are lots of special surprises, so please look forward to it!
Please listen to the next song, Undead!
unhappy?
if you're dealing with a lotta woes
unhappy? If you're dealing with a lotta woes,
unlucky?
then you got to listen very close
unlucky? Then you got to listen very close.
be happy!
keep on trying, never give up
Be happy! Keep on trying, never give up,
don't forget that you're alive
the past you have been running from
that boring future yet to come
still counseling you
oh my, oh my
universal
peace, peace yeah
universal, peace, peace yeah.
unhappy?
unlucky?
be happy!
Unhappy? Unlucky? Be happy!
undead, oh
hey, hey, hey, hey
somehow feeling like there's a fight within
and it's been going on so long
i don't feel it and don't even wanna try
past version of me, of me, of me, of me and those figures of the old
Past version of me, and those figures of the old,
transparent ghosts over my route
the childish and painful memories have the deepest roots
saddening?
nowhere to be seen
Saddening? Nowhere to be seen.
say what?
way better then? irony
Say what? Way better then? Irony.
they all see the me of the past when looking at me now
nonsense
label i can't erase
Nonsense, label I can't erase.
yes!
in essence, a complex
Yes! In essence, a complex.
it's almost like something's possessing me
it is wrapping tight around
and won't loosen its bounds
it is wrapping tight around and won't loosen its bounds.
the self i used to be before
undead, oh
The self I used to be before, undead, oh.
still alive
time is a chain of your own path
to be alive is to always embrace your inner changes, on and on
Time is a chain of your own path to be alive is to always embrace your inner changes, on and on.
don't settle for unhappiness
don't be complacent in distress
not even trying to seize the joy and be happy, you coward
oh, this world, oh, this world is one odd, one odd fantasy
Oh, this world is one odd, one odd fantasy.
who knows what is coming up next, a monster or a snake?
this is a story starting after that encounter, finally
with people or monsters and spirits
back on topic
peace, peace yeah
Back on topic, peace, peace yeah.
past & future
can't change the past
Past & future, can't change the past.
past & future
run for the future
Past & future, run for the future.
cutting in
somehow feeling like there's nothing to be looking forward to
no hope to find
cannot be defined
No hope to find, cannot be defined,
that's how i'm feeling inside
there's nothing left to view
lived long enough, nothing is new
There's nothing left to view, lived long enough, nothing is new.
no sign of anything wonderful waiting down the line
saddening
too much knowledge results in feeling like every myth is
Saddening, too much knowledge results in feeling like every myth is
but another boring evolution
thrill is what i really want now
bored and down
used to frowns
Thrill is what I really want now, bored and down, used to frowns.
and this is the way the guidance grew
rising compliance too
And this is the way the guidance grew, rising compliance too.
it's like i'm going under a lid
i consumed everything
It's like I'm going under a lid, I consumed everything.
this one or that one or, whichever
and now it all just tastes the same
undead, oh
still alive
Undead, oh, still alive.
time is a chain of your own path
in any era, your past and your future are in this very moment
fulfill the life you're set upon, and truthfully keep moving on
go for that happy ending
(Unhappy?) If you're dealing with a lotta woes
(Unlucky?) Then you got to listen very close
(Be happy) Keep on trying, never give up
(Undead, oh) Don't forget that you're alive
The past you have been running from
That boring future yet to come
Still counseling you, oh my, oh my
Universal, peace, peace, yeah
(Unhappy?)
(Unlucky?)
(Be happy)
(Undead, oh, undead, oh, undead, oh, oh, oh)
Hey, hey, hey, hey, somehow feeling like
There's a fight within and it's been going on so long
I don't feel it and (don't even wanna try)
Past version of me (of me, of me, of me)
And those figures of the old
Transparent ghosts over my route
The childish and painful memories
Have the deepest roots
(Saddening?) Nowhere to be seen
(Say what?) Way better than irony
They all see the me of the past
When looking at me now
(Nonsense) Label I can't erase
(Yes) In essence, a complex
It's almost like something's possessing me
It is wrapping tight around
And won't loosen its bounds
The self I used to be before (undead, oh)
Still alive, time is a chain of your own path
To be alive is to always embrace
Your inner changes, on and on
Don't settle for unhappiness
Don't be complacent in distress
Not even trying to seize the joy and be happy, you coward
Oh, this world, oh, this world is one odd, one odd fantasy
Who knows what is coming up next, a monster or a snake?
This is a story starting after that encounter, finally
With people or monsters and spirits
Back on topic, peace, peace yeah
Past and future
Can't change the past
Run for the future
Cu-cu-cutting in, somehow feeling like
There's nothing to be looking forward to
No hope to find (cannot be defined)
That's how I'm feeling ins —
There's nothing left to view
Lived long enough, nothing is new
No sign of anything wonderful waiting down the line
(Saddening) Too much knowledge results in feeling like every myth is but another boring evolution
(Thrill is what I really want now)
Bored and down (used to frowns)
And this is the way the guidance grew rising compliance too
It's like I'm going under a lid (I consumed everything)
This one or that one or, whichever
And now it all just tastes the same (undead, oh)
Still alive, time is a chain of your own path
In any era, your past and your future
Are in this very moment
Fulfill the life you're set upon
And truthfully keep moving on
Go for that happy ending (undead, oh)
OH, RISE UP, ピッカーン
Oh, rise up, shining!
RISE UP, ピッカーン
Rise up, shining!
OH, RISE UP, ピッカーン
Oh, rise up, shining!
RISE UP, ピッカーン
Rise up, shining!
一緒になって輝け Ready, Three, Two, One, Ahh
Shine together! Ready, Three, Two, One, Ahh
さあ どう行こう？ 焦燥 妄想 All in my head, Let's go!
Now, how should we go? Impatience, delusions, all in my head, let's go!
もう めげそう？ 無理そう てか そんなことねえ Let's go!
About to give up? Think it's impossible? No way, let's go!
やっちゃいけ (Big up!) 勝っちゃいけ (Big up!)
Do it (Big up!), win it (Big up!)
パッション バレー (Pa ra ra yeah)
Passion valley (Pa ra ra yeah)
失敗じゃない 最低もない
Not a failure, not even the lowest
再会まで 追いかけていけ
Chase it all the way until we meet again
託された想いが (Ah eh ah eh) 僕らを強くする
The feelings left behind (Ah eh ah eh) make us stronger
出会いと別れ 重なる支えを 落とさず 連れていこう
Encounters and farewells, overlap and support us, let's carry them on without dropping a single one
OH, RISE UP, ピッカーン 変えていこう やれそう 出来そう
Oh, rise up, shining! Let's change it, looks doable, seems possible
OH, RISE UP, ピッカーン RISE UP, ピッカーン
Oh, rise up, shining! Rise up, shining!
一緒になって輝け Ready, Three, Two, One, Ahh
Shine together! Ready, Three, Two, One, Ahh
(Yeah) 最高だぜ この上ない Non stop な Buddy
(Yeah) It's the best, an unparalleled, non-stop buddy
あっという間に 上がれる 限界へ (Wa wa wa wa)
In the blink of an eye, let's rise to the limit (Wa wa wa wa)
難解だって 晴れ
Even if it's difficult, it clears up
傘 なんていらないや 雨
We don't need any umbrella in the rain
Why don't you dare 掴めもうか やってやろうぜ
Why don't you dare grab it and let's do it!
Mayday 助け合えば 問題ないね
Mayday, if we help each other out, there's no problem at all
絶望に見る 希望
Finding hope within despair
明日もきみと 旅するでしょう
I'll be traveling with you tomorrow too
約束がちゃんと 待ってるんだ OK?
The promise is waiting right there for us, okay?
悲しいから泣くのは (Ah eh ah eh) もうやめ 弱くない
Crying just because you're sad (Ah eh ah eh) stop that, we aren't weak
乗り越えた壁 負けない強さを 落とさず 連れていこう
The walls we've overcome, the strength not to lose, let's bring them along without dropping them
Rise up! Make it ばつぐんな 素敵 ing 願い
Rise up! Make it an amazing, wonderful-ing wish
Rise up! Make it ポッシボな 誓った未来
Rise up! Make it a possible, sworn future
集え 叶え Three, Two, Ready? Big bang!
Gather, make it come true! Three, Two, Ready? Big bang!
上がれ 僕らのための冒険だ Go, Go (Let's go!)
Rise up, it's an adventure just for us! Go, Go (Let's go!)
半端じゃない 燃えてる想いは 上昇中
Our burning passion is halfway there, rising up high
生まれる感傷は きみの消しゴムで 消してほしい
I want you to erase any growing sentiment with your eraser
期待は好きだけ 全部 僕らのため
Expectations are just what I love, all for our own sake
Rise up! Make it ばつぐんな 素敵 ing 願い
Rise up! Make it an amazing, wonderful-ing wish
Rise up! Make it ポッシボな 誓った未来
Rise up! Make it a possible, sworn future
集え 叶え Three, Two, Ready? Big bang!
Gather, make it come true! Three, Two, Ready? Big bang!
上がれ 僕らのための冒険だ Go, Go (Let's go!)
Rise up, it's an adventure just for us! Go, Go (Let's go!)
火照る Journey その向こうに Hop, Step, Get だ
Beyond that glowing journey, it's Hop, Step, Get!
Come on, Rise up! Come on, Rise up! (Ah ah ah ah)
変えていこう やれそう 出来そう
Let's change it, looks doable, seems possible
OH, RISE UP, ピッカーン RISE UP, ピッカーン
Oh, rise up, shining! Rise up, shining!
一緒になって輝け Ready, Three, Two, One, Ahh
Shine together! Ready, Three, Two, One, Ahh
半端じゃない 燃えてる想いは 上昇中
Our burning passion is halfway there, rising up high
積もる感傷は きみの消しゴムで 消してほしい
I want you to erase any growing sentiment with your eraser
期待は好きだけ 全部 僕らのため
Expectations are just what I love, all for our own sake
Rise up! Make it ばつぐんな 素敵 ing 願い
Rise up! Make it an amazing, wonderful-ing wish
Rise up! Make it ポッシボな 誓った未来
Rise up! Make it a possible, sworn future
集え 叶え Three, Two, Ready? Big bang!
Gather, make it come true! Three, Two, Ready? Big bang!
上がれ 僕らのための冒険だ Go, Go (Let's go!)
Rise up, it's an adventure just for us! Go, Go (Let's go!)
Rise up! Make it ばつぐんな 素敵 ing 願い
Rise up! Make it an amazing, wonderful-ing wish
Rise up! Make it ポッシボな 誓った未来
Rise up! Make it a possible, sworn future
集え 叶え Three, Two, Ready? Big bang!
Gather, make it come true! Three, Two, Ready? Big bang!
上がれ 僕らのための冒険だ Go, Go (Let's go!)
Rise up, it's an adventure just for us! Go, Go (Let's go!)
ホテルジャニーズ その向こうに Hop, Step, Get だ
Beyond that glowing journey, it's Hop, Step, Get!
Come on, Rise up! Come on, Rise up! (Ah ah ah ah)
変えていこう やれそう 出来そう
Let's change it, looks doable, seems possible
OH, RISE UP, ピッカーン RISE UP, ピッカーン
Oh, rise up, shining! Rise up, shining!
一緒になって輝け Ready, Three, Two, One, Ahh
Shine together! Ready, Three, Two, One, Ahh
ライズアップ ピッカーン！ライズアップ ピッカーン！
Oh, rise up, shining! Rise up, shining!
こんにちわ こんにちわ
Hello, hello!
Okay, okay, okay, let's do self-introduction, even though they don't really need one.
Okay, okay, okay. Let's do self-introductions, even though they don't really need one.
Let's start with the senpai.
Yay!
ハロー！フィフ…フィフジェネレ…もう文字ずれない！
Hello! Fifu... Fifujeneresho... My text is misaligned!
フィフズじゃないだっけ？フィフズ？フィフズジェネレーション！
Wasn't it Fifuz? Fifuz? Fifuz generation!
イェーイ！ジェネレーション！
Yay! Generation!
どう、後輩？
How is it, kouhai?
ハロー！ホロックス！いろは風でござる！
Hello! HoloX! It's Iroha, in the wind!
イェーイ！
Yay!
ってあまり英語入ってなかった気がする。
I feel like there wasn't much English in that.
There's not enough English! 難しいでそう difficult sorry 海外にけ
There's not enough English! It's so difficult, sorry, to overseas!
イェーイ！オッケー！ネネち！
Yay! Okay! Nenechi!
It's been a while. 久しぶりだね。
It's been a while. It's been a while.
It's been a while! Wow!
Two years? Maybe two years that we danced together.
Long time ago! Long time ago! Last year no?
Last year! Yeah, last year! Last year!
Yay! I'm happy, happy! Yay, happy, happy!
I feel like our colors match very well, right?
So maybe if Nenechi is in the middle...
Oh, look! Gradation! Gradation! Yay!
Blonde, blonde, beach, orange, yellow!
Beautiful! 目の色、髪の色。
Beautiful! Eye color, hair color.
え、いろはちゃん？あ、確かに！いろはちゃん、アイカラー in my hair.
Eh, Iroha-chan? Ah, true! Iroha-chan, eye color in my hair.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes! Beautiful!
シナジーを感じる！ということでシナジー。
I feel synergy! So, synergy.
えっと、the song we just sang together, we cannot say too clearly what it was all about, but...
Um, the song we just sang together, we cannot say too clearly what it was all about, but...
did you see this pose here? Pose? What is this pose?
I wonder, we're holding some kind of ball here.
But it could also very well be baseball? Baseball? Baseball kana? Yakyuu?
ということで、I want everybody to show me an original throwing pose, okay? Challenge!
So, I want everybody to show me an original throwing pose, okay? Challenge!
Ikkai, ikkai throw. Yes, yes! Okay, kakkoiiro!
Once, once, throw. Yes, yes! Okay, cool!
Kawaii, nandemo ok! I start, ok? I start! Ok.
Cute, anything is fine! I start, ok? I start! Ok.
Here we go, ball throwing challenge! Three, two, one, hoi! Hoi!
Kakkoii! Sexy! Kakkoii! Sexy! Kakkoii!
Cool! Sexy! Cool! Sexy! Cool!
Ok, ok! Next? Dare dare? Fuman-sazu? Nene, nene, nene, nene!
Ok, ok! Next? Who, who? Dissatisfied? Nene, nene, nene, nene!
Miru, miru, miru, let's go! Ikkai!
Watch, watch, watch, let's go! Once!
Volley... Volleyball! Volleyball janai! Ok, ok! Kiotsuke!
Volley... Volleyball! Not volleyball! Ok, ok! Attention!
Very cute! Very cute! Yeah, Iroha-chan.
いろはちゃんもそういうの欲しいな。なんかクールなことやってなんか引き増しますよ。
Iroha wants something like that too. Doing something cool and pulling back.
引いてくれるかな？
Will you pull it off for me?
Poon kara no... Jakii!
Poon, and then... Jakii!
Nice jakii, jakii! またつまらぬものを切ったでござる。
Nice jakii, jakii! Another boring thing has come, forsooth.
Very nice, very nice! The viewers and audience maybe can tell us which one was best, but...
For now, because I still have many more guests and many more songs, I have to take this jacket off, so please...
お着替え！着替えます！
Change clothes! I'll change clothes!
Hayaku shanakya! Chotto matte! Chotto matte! Kakuseki! Kakuseki!
Gotta hurry! Wait a minute! Wait a minute! Kakuseki! Kakuseki!
Te tte tte, otte otte, o kigae!
Hands hands hands, waiting waiting, changing clothes!
Thank you! Thank you! Kawaii!
Thank you! Thank you! Cute!
So, we already have to say goodbye, mou baibai no jikan desu ne.
So, we already have to say goodbye, it's already time to say bye-bye.
Demo arigatou! Thank you! Tanoshikatta! Tanoshikatta!
But thank you! Thank you! It was fun! It was fun!
Ja, tsugi no kyoku mo ganbatte ne! Ganbatte kudasai!
Well, do your best on the next song too! Please do your best!
Paipai! Baibai! Baibai! Baibai!
Paipai! Bye-bye! Bye-bye! Bye-bye!
can i get it get it get all your attention
i bet you don’t know me yet
君の奥底まで 穿つ視点で
Piercing gaze to the depths of your soul
溢れる様 iq ammo
Overflowing, like IQ ammo
獲る天下 a catalyst, i know. when i say go, put your hands up
Claiming the world, a catalyst, I know. When I say go, put your hands up!
混沌の最中に 降臨した女神
A goddess descending into the midst of chaos
i freeze it up, got it ice cold on my body
you wanna know but you don’t 震わせる異脳
You wanna know, but you don't, shaking strange minds
i’mma go, i’mma shine, shine, shine, shine
I'mma go, I'mma shine, shine, shine, shine
can’t stop 煌めく my fantasy now you see
Can't stop glowing, my fantasy, now you see
星空を咀嚼 染めるんだ私色に
Chewing the starry sky, dyeing it in my colors
hidden deep within my universe come find me now
hear the voice that’s calling out
Hear the voice that's calling out
まだ見えぬ世界の真贋を見せてあげるから baby, for now
I'll show you the truth of a world yet unseen, baby, for now
I know what I came to do
And that ain't gonna change
So go ahead and talk your talk
'Cause I won't take the bait
I'm over here doing what I like
I'm over here working day and night
And if my real ain't real enough
I'm sorry for you bae
Let's find a light inside our universe now
Where ain't nobody keep on holding us down
Just come and get it let them say what they say
'Cause I'm about to put them all away
Focus on me
Foc foc
Focus on me focus
Focus on me focus on me
Foc foc
I can tell you're curious
It's written on your lips
Ain't no need to hold it back
Go head and talk
I know you're hoping that I'll react
I know you're hoping I'm looking back
But if my real ain't real enough
Then I don't know what is
Let's find a light inside our universe now
Where ain't nobody keep on holding us down
Just come and get it let them say what they say
'Cause I'm about to put them all away
Focus on me
Foc foc
Focus on me focus
Focus on me focus on me
Foc foc
One two three
Come on girls
You know I like it
Focus on me
Come on now
Yeah yeah
Let's find a light inside our universe now
Where ain't nobody keep on holding us down
Just come and get it let them say what they say
'Cause I'm about to put them all away
Focus on me
Foc foc
Focus on me you know
I like it when you focus on me
Focus on me
Foc foc
Focus on me focus on me
Focus foc foc
Focus on me
Focus on me focus on me
Focus foc foc
Focus on me
Focus on me focus on me
Foc foc
Focus on me
Focus on me focus
Foc foc
Focus on me focus on me
Focus on me focus
Foc foc
Focus on me focus on me
I know what I came to do
And that ain't gonna change
So go ahead and talk your talk
'Cause I won't take the bait
I'm over here doing what I like
I'm over here working day and night
And if my real ain't real enough
I'm sorry for you bae
Let's find a light inside our universe now
Where ain't nobody keep on holding us down
Just come and get it let them say what they say
'Cause I'm about to put them all away
Focus on me
Foc foc
Focus on me focus
Focus on me focus on me
Foc foc
I can tell you're curious
It's written on your lips
Ain't no need to hold it back
Go head and talk
I know you're hoping that I'll react
I know you're hoping I'm looking back
But if my real ain't real enough
Then I don't know what is
Let's find a light inside our universe now
Where ain't nobody keep on holding us down
Just come and get it let them say what they say
'Cause I'm about to put them all away
Focus on me
Foc foc
Focus on me focus
Focus on me focus on me
Foc foc
One two three
Come on girls
You know I like it
Focus on me
Come on now
Yeah yeah
Let's find a light inside our universe now
Where ain't nobody keep on holding us down
Just come and get it let them say what they say
'Cause I'm about to put them all away
Focus on me
Foc foc
Focus on me you know
I like it when you focus on me
Focus on me
Foc foc
Focus on me focus on me
Focus foc foc
Focus on me
Focus on me focus on me
Focus foc foc
Focus on me
Focus on me focus on me
Foc foc
Focus on me
Focus on me focus
Foc foc
Focus on me focus on me
Focus on me focus
Foc foc
Focus on me focus on me
とべ、起こせ！願うは事変
Get excited and seek thrills! Hoping for an accident to happen
一世一代さあ何賭ける？ 自問自答
This happens once in a lifetime, so what are you going to bet on? Self-questioning
勝つか負けるかドローなんてないわ
Is it a win or a loss? There's no such thing as a draw
幕開けるわ
The curtain is about to rise
カッチングして ラッキー マニー
Game starts, lucky money
どっちもむりー …
Getting nothing...
余裕で！振り切り全 bet だぜ イェイ イェイ ☆
With ease! Breaking through and going all-in, bet everything, yeah yeah!
そこどけ！そうこのエース
Step aside! Yes, this ace
かっさらうのは アタシだ
Is going to be snatched away by me
stay もういい 勝ったなら平常心
Stay, that's enough, once you win, keep a calm mind
ね プレイボーイ 行けよ
Hey playboy, go ahead
don’t get in my way じゃあね 黙って
Don't get in my way, see ya, shut up
ワンツースリー
One, two, three
sit down , sit down
Sit down, sit down
ワンツースリー
One, two, three
はーもう フリーズ キメ て やん
Ah, reaction is already sluggish, come take a puff
投げる のは さい ？ 才 ？ か 匙 か ？
What's being thrown? Dice? Talent? Or hope?
そんな 小さい 尺 じゃ はかれない
Such a tiny scale can't measure it
でしょ ♪ そうでしょ ♪ セイ ・ グッド ・ バイ ✋
Right? Is that so? Say goodbye
あっちこっち そっちどっち ？
Here, there, everywhere, which way?
nothing , nothing 病む
Nothing, nothing, falling sick
道 なき 道 より 闇 々 恋
Worse than a pathless path, deep darkness, so distressing
空回り しそう でも まだ 止め ないで
Seems like it's going to be all for nothing, but don't stop yet
あー の まれ そう 声 々 、 それぞれ に
Ah, about to be swallowed up, voices intertwine, each in their own way
get one ’s way !
Get one's way!
アンタ は ここ まで
You've reached your limit
後ろ だけ 見 とけ
Just watch your back
カッチングして ラッキー マニー
Game starts, lucky money
どっち も むりー ！
Getting nothing!
引ける か 否 か 自分 次第 だ な
Whether you can pull it off or not depends on yourself, huh?
余裕 で ！ 振り切り 全 bet だぜ イェイ イェイ ☆
With ease! Breaking through and going all-in, bet everything, yeah yeah!
そこ どけ ！ そう この エース
Step aside! Yes, this ace
かっさら う の は アタシ だ
Is going to be snatched away by me
stay もう いい 勝た なら 平常心
Stay, that's enough, once you win, keep a calm mind
ね プレイボーイ 行け よ
Hey playboy, go ahead
don’t get in my way じゃあ ね 黙って
Don't get in my way, see ya, shut up
ワンツースリー
One, two, three
sit down , sit down
Sit down, sit down
ワンツースリー
One, two, three
まさかの 倍 倍 ＄
An unexpected double $
ワンツースリー
One, two, three
sit down , sit down
Sit down, sit down
ワンツースリー
One, two, three
sit down , sit down
Sit down, sit down
とべ、起こせ！
Jump, wake it up!
願うは事変
What we wish for is an incident.
sit down, sit down
ワンツー３ ワンツー３ ワンツー３
One two three, one two three, one two three.
まさかのバイバイ
An unexpected goodbye.
ワンツー３ ワンツー３ ワンツー３
One two three, one two three, one two three.
sit down, sit down
ワンツー３ ワンツー３ ワンツー３
One two three, one two three, one two three.
sit down, sit down
I like em' tall
he's my 完璧な究極体
he's my perfect, ultimate form.
必要なのは
All that's needed
ただ numbers, encode
is just numbers, encode.
I'm a creator
無敵な創造主
an invincible creator.
いくらでもクリック
Click as much as you want,
need it, make it, snap that!
一線を越えると
Once you cross the line,
天国も歪曲
even paradise is distorted.
need it, make it, snap that!
疲れ果ててもう信じたくない
Exhausted, I don't want to believe anymore.
oh he's an ace 僕のためだけ toy
Oh, he's an ace, a toy just for me.
愛される契約 imai ma yuh ima
A contract to be loved, imai ma yuh ima.
puzzle pieces of love 今完璧にフィットする
Puzzle pieces of love fitting perfectly now.
fake heart, fake heart
puzzle pieces of love もっと僕の仕様に
puzzle pieces of love, tailored to my specs.
start it up and complete fa-fa-fake heart
fa-fa-fake heart fa-fake, then バラバラ
Fa-fa-fake heart, fa-fake, then falling apart.
ooh i ~ 何度も restart it
Ooh I~, restarting it over and over,
perfect is my target
what's the matter? w-what's the matter?
より良い世界へ変えていきましょう
Let's change it into a better world.
c-c-click agree 誰でも神に yea
C-c-click agree, playing god to anyone, yea.
リセットするか boom boom boom!
Resetting or boom boom boom!
ようこそ僕の playground 未来の展示会さ
Welcome to my playground, a future exhibition.
100%満足約束しますから
I promise 100% satisfaction.
有機的とか時代遅れ ついてきなさい
Organic stuff is outdated, just follow along.
no love? 聞くな
No love? Didn't ask.
no job? 残念！
No job? Too bad!
執着したキミの fault
It's your fault for getting so attached.
疲れ果ててもう信じたくない
Exhausted, I don't want to believe anymore.
oh he's an ace 僕のためだけ toy
Oh, he's an ace, a toy just for me.
愛される契約 imai ma yuh ima
A contract to be loved, imai ma yuh ima.
puzzle pieces of love 今完璧にフィットする
Puzzle pieces of love fitting perfectly now.
fake heart, fake heart
puzzle pieces of love もっと僕の仕様に
puzzle pieces of love, tailored to my specs.
start it up and complete fa-fa-fake heart
fa-fa-fake heart fa-fake, then バラバラ
Fa-fa-fake heart, fa-fake, then falling apart.
ooh i ~ 何度も restart it
Ooh I~, restarting it over and over,
perfect is my target
夢か現実か どちらでもいい
Dream or reality, either is fine.
理想に溺れたい
I want to drown in ideals.
今日も華麗にプログラム プログラム
Today too, brilliantly programming, programming.
実現まで急ぐ命は短し
Life is short when rushing to make it real.
perfect! naa, again! yeah
何が悪いわけ？
What's even wrong with that?
puzzle pieces of love 今完璧にフィットする
Puzzle pieces of love fitting perfectly now.
fake heart, fake heart
puzzle pieces of love もっと僕の仕様に
puzzle pieces of love, tailored to my specs.
start it up and complete
follow follow like it like it
結局人生はフィクション
after all, life is fiction.
follow follow like it like it
はいどうぞ！ニュー中毒
here you go! A brand new addiction.
follow follow like it like it
はまったらもう最後
once you're hooked, it's the end.
follow follow like it like it
楽しんで！
enjoy it!
my heart starts skipping a beat
繙いた 新章
a newly unraveled chapter.
様変わりしてゆく show time
A changing show time,
全然悪くない イマジネーション
an imagination that isn't bad at all.
視界の霧は晴れ渡り
The fog in my vision clears up,
悲しみに別れを告げる
saying goodbye to sadness.
酸いも甘いも穹に放り出して
Throwing both the sweet and sour into the void,
滲む空 インクは薔薇色
the ink in the blurring sky is rose-colored.
どれだけ上手く魅せようとしても
No matter how well I try to look appealing,
キミがいなければ
without you,
何の意味もない
it has no meaning at all.
擦り傷すらつかない 幻想
An illusion that won't even leave a scratch,
針の落ちない レコード さ
a record where the needle never drops.
たった今 止め処ない追い風 背にして
Right now, with an unstoppable tailwind at my back,
come on, let's roll
my heart starts skipping a beat
紐解いた新章
Unraveling a new chapter
様変わりしてゆく show time
A transforming show time
全然悪くないイマジネーション
An imagination that's not bad at all
視界の霧は晴れ渡って
The fog in my vision clears up
悲しみに訣別を告げる
Bidding farewell to sadness
酸いも甘いも宙に放り出して
Throwing both sweet and sour into the air
滲む空 インクは薔薇色
The blurring sky, the ink is rose-colored
どれだけ上手く魅せようとしても
No matter how well I try to make it look
キミがいなければ
If you aren't here,
なんの意味もない
It has no meaning at all
擦り傷すらつかない 幻想
An illusion where not even a scratch is made
針の落ちないレコードさ
A record where the needle never drops
たった今止め処ない追い風にして
Making it a ceaseless tailwind right now
come on, let's roll
芳醇と吹き荒れる向かい風にもココロ靡かせて
Letting my heart sway even against the rich, raging headwinds
飛び乗って to the future
Jump on to the future
フライングしたって alright
It's alright to jump the gun
restart line!!
ときめいてしまえば 瞬く間に広がる開放区
Once my heart flutters, an open zone spreads in the blink of an eye
ひとつひとつ すべてがドラマ
Every single thing is a drama
待ちわびた daybreak
A long-awaited daybreak
restart line!!
代わる代わる 彩る パノラマ
A changing, colorful panorama
満ち溢れる フィーリンググラデーション
A brimming feeling gradation
始まりのその時が来た
When the time of the beginning has come
nothing is impossible
マヤカシ誤魔化し効かない世界
A world where deception and pretense don't work
この先はまだ誰も知らない世界
A world whose future no one knows yet
傍観してるだけじゃ味気ない
Just watching from the sidelines is dull
リアルタイムで通じ合って
Connecting in real time
振り子にかけるエモーション
Emotion swaying like a pendulum
後々の祭りでも i don't mind
Even if it's too late later, I don't mind
大胆不敵なシチュエーション
A daring and fearless situation
行けるところまで行ってみたい
I want to go as far as I can
選択肢にない get off on the way
Not an option, get off on the way
共鳴して声を鳴らす
Resonating our voices together
素肌を貫くような真っ直ぐな痛みが伴っても
Even if accompanied by a straight pain piercing through bare skin
この仲間達と最果てまで keep running to the end
With these comrades all the way to the farthest end, keep running to the end
keep running to the end
飛び乗って to the future
Jump on to the future
フライングしたって alright
It's alright to jump the gun
restart line!!
ときめいてしまえば 瞬く間に広がる開放区
Once my heart flutters, an open zone spreads in the blink of an eye
ひとつひとつ すべてがドラマ
Every single thing is a drama
待ちわびた daybreak
A long-awaited daybreak
restart line!!
代わる代わる 彩る パノラマ
A changing, colorful panorama
満ち溢れる フィーリンググラデーション
A brimming feeling gradation
飛び出せ you raise me up
Jump out, you raise me up
恐れるものはない
There's nothing to fear
restart line!!
麗らかな朝焼けが不透明な明日にを照らすよ
A serene morning glow illuminates an opaque tomorrow
restart line!!
求メナイ明日を蹴散らすよ
Kicking away the unwanted tomorrow
restart line!!
Happy Birthday!
Happy Birthday, Kiara-senpai!
Thank you, thank you!
Well, you're wishing me happy birthday, but since we went to Austria together,
can you say it in German? Happy birthday?
Sure! Sure, sure, sure!
Okay, I'll teach you, I'll teach you. You don't know, right?
I- I don't know, sorry.
よかった
Good.
And it's Alles Gute... Alles Gute...
Gute? Gute? - Alles Gute? Alles Gute zum...
zum Geburtstag!
Geburtstag!
Okay! Okay! せーの！
Okay! Okay! Ready, go!
Alles Gute zum Geburtstag!
もはやドイツかオーストリア人やった！
We're basically German or Austrian now!
やった！
Yay!
Thank you! Super danke! Super danke!
自己紹介 in English! OK!
Self-introduction in English! Okay!
誰から？ リリカ！
From who? Ririka!
Hi! Hello everyone!
かわいいポジティブエナジーニアス！ I'm ReGLOSS from Hololive Device! ReGLOSS nice to meet you!
Kawaii positive and energetic genius! I'm ReGLOSS from Hololive Device! ReGLOSS nice to meet you!
And next! Hello everyone!
えー、17テラバイト、フロム、ホロライブデパイス、リーゴロス！イェーイ！
Um, 17 terabytes from Hololive device ReGLOSS! Yay!
ペラペラペラペラペラペラペラ
Chatter chatter chatter chatter...
Okay, everyone, we danced your song together!
イェーイ！ Thank you! Thank you!
Yay! Thank you! Thank you!
I'm so happy! ピーリングラデーション！イェース！
I'm so happy! Peeling gradation! Yes!
I felt, I'm feeling very happy to be able to dance this song 'cause it's so cool, めっちゃかっこいい曲！
I'm feeling very happy to be able to dance this song 'cause it's so cool, such a cool song!
やった！ How was it to dance with like a non-ReGLOSS member?
Yay! How was it to dance with, like, a non-ReGLOSS member?
It's actually first time to dance together with someone who is not ReGLOSS member, so I was a little bit nervous...
It's actually my first time to dance together with someone who is not a ReGLOSS member, so I was a little bit nervous...
でも！ Finally we can do it! イェーイ！Happy!
But! Finally we can do it! Yay! Happy!
I think, you know, I chose the white version of this outfit because I thought we look so good together!
Pretty on you! Yay!
So, because we look so good together, let's take a cute picture, okay?
Okay, okay! Strike a pose!
But I will go like here. No? Closer, closer, closer!
Okay! Screenshot, screenshot!
Yeah! Screenshot! Yay!
Thank you, thank you! I had so much fun!
Me too! Dance again! スーパーダッケ！スーパーダッケ！
Me too! Dance again! Super thanks! Super thanks!
じゃあ、フィーリングラデーションをリーグロスノこの可愛いおふたりと一緒に踊りましたけども！
So, we danced "Feeling Gradation" together with these two cute ReGLOSS members!
I have even more guests coming and even more songs coming! And for that, I will go to the center stage!
Oh, super thanks! Super thanks! スーパーダッケ！ 頑張れ、頑張れ！
Oh, super thanks! Super thanks! Do your best, do your best!
帰ろう！
Let's go home!
でであえやでであえ 孤独持ち寄って
Encounter, encounter, gathering our solitude,
祝えば宴 大胆な幕開け
Let's celebrate with a feast, a bold curtain-raiser!
つまらない？くだらない？ならダンス・ダンス・ダンス
Boring? Worthless? Then dance, dance, dance!
ありきたりたり 毎日ちょっとと抜け出し
Slipping away just a bit every ordinary day,
欲しがってんのは最新型の情動
What we crave is the latest model of emotion.
それでも無限永遠不滅の超常
Yet infinite, eternal, and indestructible wonder—
焦燥だって上等じゃん 今を生きてる
Impatience is fine too, we are living in the present!
愛してバースデイ
Love you, birthday!
どぅわわ ときめきにネバギバ
Wow-wow, never give up on the excitement,
連れ出して 連れ出して その歌で
Lead me out, lead me out with that song!
オンリーハッピーバースデイ
Only Happy Birthday!
そぅらら 僕らが出逢えば
So-la-la, if we meet,
特別映えるワンシーン 愛でたいな祝いを
It's a special, shining one scene, let's celebrate with love!
解けたシュウレーズ 結び直して
Untied shoelaces, tied them back up,
道なき道へ don't look back, no way no way
Heading to a pathless road, don't look back, no way no way!
なるようになってる生き様 ほら公開中
Living life as it goes, look, it's on public view!
失敗談も自己流のオール特注
Even tales of failure are custom-made in our own style,
欠けているところがオリジナル
The parts where we fall short are what make us original!
おぅなな 涙を伸ばした
Oh-na-na, stretching out the tears,
その分だけ星になれ 煌めいて
Become a star for that much, sparkling bright!
ロンリーハッピーバースデイ
Lonely Happy Birthday!
ふぅわわ 筆先がふるえた
Fu-wa-wa, the brush tip trembled,
あの日にかかったマジックが未だにとけない
The magic cast on us that day still hasn't worn off.
ひとりきり越えた夜の踊り場
The night's dancing floor crossed all alone,
与えられた答えなんかきっと合点がゆくまい bae bae
The given answers surely won't make sense, bae bae!
超ヘキレキしたいの now or never
We want to break boundaries, now or never,
出し抜く運命は絶景
Outsmarting destiny is a magnificent view!
ロンリー ロンリー アンラッキー バースデイ
Lonely, lonely, unlucky birthday,
全部持ってけ ロンリー ロンリーネス ei a ya let's go
Take it all away, lonely loneliness, ei a ya let's go!
オンリー オンリー ハッピー ラッキー バースデイ
Only, only, happy lucky birthday,
手出しな！ オンリー オンリー オール
Don't mess with us! Only, only all!
どぅわわ 僕たちはネバギバ
Wow-wow, we are never give up,
踊らせて 踊らせて この宴
Make us dance, make us dance in this feast!
オンリーハッピーバースデイ
Only Happy Birthday!
あ！あ！あ！あ！あなたを見つけた
Ah! Ah! Ah! Ah! I found you!
瞬き 色めき立つ 新世界へ
Into the blinking, dazzling new world,
愛してバースデイ
Love you, birthday!
i what what need sparkle, oh never give up!
変わっていくこの響きは変わらずに
This changing echo remains unchanged,
la la hit you up! see you later!
合図をここから君に送信
Sending the signal to you from right here.
愛してるよ ずっと愛すべき僕らへ
I love you, to all of us who deserve to be loved forever!
ロンリー ロンリー アンラッキー バースデイ
Lonely, lonely, unlucky birthday,
手出しな！ ロンリー ロンリーネス hey, hey, bae bae 祝おうか
Don't mess with us! Lonely loneliness, hey, hey, bae bae, let's celebrate!
オンリー オンリー ハッピー ラッキー バースデイ
Only, only, happy lucky birthday,
手あげな！ オンリーラブラブ オール
Put your hands up! Only love-love all!
愛してバースデイ
Love you, birthday!
Let me know
どこで どんな
Where and what kind of
景色を見てる？
scenery are you looking at?
君に続く are you? anything anywhere
Leading to you, are you? Anything, anywhere
こんな地図のさし示す方へ
Toward the direction this map points,
君の足取りたどりながら
tracing your footsteps as I go.
憧れを力に変えて
Turning my yearning into strength,
rock my world, baby
あれからどれくらい君に
How long has it been since then
追い続けただろう いつでも前を行く
that I've kept chasing you, always staying ahead?
その背中を見つめ続けてきた
I've kept gazing at that back of yours.
遠い道のり
A long road,
越えて行くたびに
every time I overcome it,
本当の強さの
I learn the meaning
意味を知るから
of true strength.
すべてを投げ出したとしたとしてもまだ
Even if I were to throw everything away, still
君との距離感 詰め切れなくて
I still can't close the distance between us.
あの日々 あの時 思いを起こせば
If I recall those days, that time,
この想いを届けて
delivering these feelings.
どこで どんな
Where and what kind of
景色を見てる？
scenery are you looking at?
君に続く
Leading to you,
are you? anything anywhere
いつかは誰かが私の
Someday, someone might become
背中を追うようになるかも
the one chasing my back,
それでもペースは落とさずに run to you, baby
yet without slowing my pace, run to you, baby.
振り返らずにゴールを目指し走ってく
Running toward the goal without looking back,
いつも自分がいた時の上にいることだけ信じて
believing only in being above the time I was always in.
たとえ何度も
No matter how many times
壁を感じても
I feel the wall,
今の道を乗り越えて見せる
I will overcome this path now.
すべてを投げ出したとしたとしてもまだ
Even if I were to throw everything away, still
君との距離感 詰め切れなくて
I still can't close the distance between us.
あの日々 あの時 思いを起こせば
If I recall those days, that time,
この想いを届けて
delivering these feelings.
どこで どんな
Where and what kind of
景色を見てる？
scenery are you looking at?
君に続く
Leading to you,
are you? anything anywhere
また君と会える日を信じて
Believing in the day I can meet you again,
受け止めた想いを未来へと
carrying the feelings I accepted toward the future,
届けるのさ
delivering them.
すべてを投げ出したとしたとしてもまだ
Even if I were to throw everything away, still
君との距離感 詰め切れなくて
I still can't close the distance between us.
あの日々 あの時 思いを起こせば
If I recall those days, that time,
この想いを届けて
delivering these feelings.
どこで どんな
Where and what kind of
景色を見てる？
scenery are you looking at?
君に続く
Leading to you,
are you? anything anywhere
Let me know
One for the one
Ah 海岸沿い 貸した奴らが集まるあの店 二人のステージ
Ah, that shop by the coast where shady people gather, our stage.
Ah 双子みたいにバッチリ まつげは今日も潮風 受け止めているわ
Ah, like twins, our eyelashes perfectly catch the sea breeze today too.
二人踊り出したらほら誰にも負けないわ
When the two of us start dancing, look, we won't lose to anyone.
Step!! Baby...let's dance tonight!!!
Step!! Baby... let's dance tonight!!!
海岸通りの噂 アタシたちのモノにするわ 逃さない
The rumor along the coastal street is ours, we'll make it ours, won't let it escape.
come on! come on! come on! my darlin'
潮騒に踊る 君とアタシは 今も昔もレディマーメイド
Dancing to the sound of waves, you and I are lady mermaids, now as then.
Hey Boy!!! 恋もクルマも夏は渋滞さ
Hey Boy!!! Both romance and cars are congested in summer.
恋は そう、いつでも愚か
Love is yes, always foolish,
持ってるもの全部なくしても 会いたいのに
Even if I lose everything I have, I want to see you,
I’m Mermaid 海の泡となって
I’m Mermaid, turning into the foam of the sea,
いつの日か消えてゆくとわかっていても...
Even knowing that someday I will fade away...
愛に生きた人魚のように
Like a mermaid who lived for love,
あなたを待つフィヨルドで
In the fjord waiting for you,
偶然よ、どうかな運命になれ
Coincidence, please become fate,
月灯り頼りにして 影を探したの
Relying on the moonlight, I searched for your shadow,
髪を飾る真珠の粒ねえ、涙にしないで
The pearls decorating your hair, hey, don't turn them into tears,
一夜でいい その腕に抱きしめられたい
Even just for one night, I want to be held in those arms,
Foolish Foolish Love
(届きますか)
(Can you hear me?),
恋は ああ、美しい歌奏でるけど
Love, ah, plays a beautiful song,
会えなきゃ声がないのと同じ
But if we can't meet, it's the same as having no voice,
I’m Mermaid 海の青が切なさで滲む
I’m Mermaid, the blue of the sea blurs with sorrow,
百の嘘でも隠せない
Even a hundred lies cannot hide it,
“私、あなたが好きです”
"I love you."
難破船も無人島も
Whether a shipwreck or a desert island,
一緒にいれたなら楽園
If we could be together, it's a utopia,
砂の城に嫉妬心を そっと閉じ込めたの
I softly locked away jealousy in a sandcastle,
耳朶で揺れるアクアマリン ねえ、吐息で焦がして
Aquamarine swaying at my earlobe, hey, burn me with your sigh,
一度でいい イーブンに想い合えたら
If just once we could feel equally for each other,
Fallin’ Fallin’ Down
(燃え尽きましょう)
(Let's burn out),
恋は そう、いつでも愚か
Love is yes, always foolish,
持ってるもの全部なくしても 会いたいのに
Even if I lose everything I have, I want to see you,
I’m Mermaid 海の泡となって
I’m Mermaid, turning into the foam of the sea,
いつの日か消えてゆくとわかっていても...
Even knowing that someday I will fade away...
愛に生きた人魚のように
Like a mermaid who lived for love,
望んでかかった魔法が 幸せとは限らなくて
The magic I wished for isn't necessarily happiness,
それでも胸 いっぱいの愛で
Even so, with all my heart and a full measure of love,
で溺れる くらいに 呼吸を させて
Let me breathe until I drown,
(届きますか)
(Can you hear me?),
恋は ああ、美しい歌奏でる けど
Love, ah, plays a beautiful song,
会えなきゃ 声がない の と 同じ
But if we can't meet, it's the same as having no voice,
I’m Mermaid 海の 青 に い と し さ が 溶ける
I’m Mermaid, love melts into the blue of the sea,
千の波 と 永遠に
Forever with a thousand waves,
恋 は そう 、 何 より 尊い
Love is yes, more precious than anything,
持ってるもの全部なくしても 会いたいのに
Even if I lose everything I have, I want to see you,
I’m Mermaid 海の泡となって
I’m Mermaid, turning into the foam of the sea,
いつの日か 消えてゆく 勇気 捧 げ たい
I want to offer the courage to fade away someday,
“私、あなたが好きです”
"I love you."
恋は そう、いつでも愚か
Love is yes, always foolish,
持ってるもの全部なくしても 会いたいのに
Even if I lose everything I have, I want to see you,
I’m Mermaid 海の泡となって
I’m Mermaid, turning into the foam of the sea,
いつの日か消えてゆくとわかっていても...
Even knowing that someday I will fade away...
愛に生きた人魚のように
Like a mermaid who lived for love,
あなたを待つフィヨルドで
In the fjord waiting for you,
偶然よ、どうかな運命になれ
Coincidence, please become fate,
月灯り頼りにして 影を探したの
Relying on the moonlight, I searched for your shadow,
髪を飾る真珠の粒ねえ、涙にしないで
The pearls decorating your hair, hey, don't turn them into tears,
一夜でいい その腕に抱きしめられたい
Even just for one night, I want to be held in those arms,
Foolish Foolish Love
(届きますか)
(Can you hear me?),
恋は ああ、美しい歌奏でるけど
Love, ah, plays a beautiful song,
会えなきゃ声がないのと同じ
But if we can't meet, it's the same as having no voice,
I’m Mermaid 海の青が切なさで滲む
I’m Mermaid, the blue of the sea blurs with sorrow,
百の嘘でも隠せない
Even a hundred lies cannot hide it,
“私、あなたが好きです”
"I love you."
難破船も無人島も
Whether a shipwreck or a desert island,
一緒にいれたなら楽園
If we could be together, it's a utopia,
砂の城に嫉妬心を そっと閉じ込めたの
I softly locked away jealousy in a sandcastle,
耳朶で揺れるアクアマリン ねえ、吐息で焦がして
Aquamarine swaying at my earlobe, hey, burn me with your sigh,
一度でいい イーブンに想い合えたら
If just once we could feel equally for each other,
Fallin’ Fallin’ Down
(燃え尽きましょう)
(Let's burn out),
恋は そう、いつでも愚か
Love is yes, always foolish,
持ってるもの全部なくしても 会いたいのに
Even if I lose everything I have, I want to see you,
I’m Mermaid 海の泡となって
I’m Mermaid, turning into the foam of the sea,
いつの日か 消えてゆく 勇気 捧 げ たい
I want to offer the courage to fade away someday,
One for the one
Woo! We did it! We did it! Okay!
Let's start right ahead with the introduction!
Hello everybody, my name is Mint Fantome. I am a cosumed... VTuber!
I'm not a part of Hololive, but I am a big fan of Mr. Takanashi Kiara!
It is our first ever 3D appearance together, and we sang a beautiful song...
...that I think means a lot to both of us. What's it called? It was Lady Mermaid.
From two beautiful ladies from Hello! Project, Suzuki Airi and Sugaya Risako.
But by now you guys should really remember those names!
so the Easter live that I had, okay?
Yeah, yeah, yeah. So it's teleparted all over again. We had a lot of fun with that, right?
We did!
Practicing to Gamba,
shaking the booby!
When we were doing crackett, every time we would like do the
this part, we would stare at each other, shake the booby!
So fun.
Yeah.
I'm so happy that we're together and you're here!
I know.
It's like... It's like, you almost say, it really does feel like this is a different timeline where somehow you ended up here.
Yeah.
Maybe.
Is this kind of fun to like...
Today I'm roleplaying.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
A little bit.
Ooh, I wonder which generation you're from if you're roleplaying.
And then I also got to see the big wall of the signatures and everything.
Yeah, it's been really exciting being here at the Hololive Studio, so
thank you everybody. Thank you Kiara.
Thank you for having me.
Yeah, it's my first time having an external guest,
so that's exciting.
Oh, really?
Yeah.
Woah! Yeah, I've been like kind of trying to get something going for a while,
but it never worked out.
But now, finally, you're ready. Like, I was going to like honestly
invite you earlier, but you know, it took you a while to become this.
I feel too... I feel too honored for this.
I feel like I'm too small for this position.
I feel like I'm so real goddammit.
Okay. Okay.
So, anyway,
this was a special time, but so
fact is,
fact of the matter is, you are a maid,
Yes.
and you have to like kind of pay for this exposure I've given you.
Oh, oh, I see.
So, I would like you to clean the stage, please, 'cause there's dirt, dirt, dirt, dirt.
Oh, get rid of it! Where did this come from?
You're a maid, right? Clean it up!
I have no materials. I'll just use my hands.
Why is it not going away?
You're so bad at this! I'm sorry, you goddamn it.
Oh, let me kiss your feet.
You better. All the KFP are crying right now.
Get to work!
It's not going away! Mama mia! Oh my god!
Can you not do anything right?
I'm sorry. Joseph, please forgive me. Don't kick me out.
No, I will not forgive you! I will show you how it's done.
Okay. Yeah? Okay.
I am going to get you!
Turn it up to the top
Let’s get it started, go non-stop
Bust through the door, we don’t knock (just have a good time)
Like we never cared about what they say
Tear up the place like it’s our own
Get wilder than a cyclone
And leave it on a high note
It’s just like magic lighting up the sky
When we’re together we don’t have to try
If you wanna join then this is your invite
Show ’em what you got, come on don’t be shy!
We, we are breaking through borders
Free, like the clouds are beneath us, oh
We, we’re like diamonds in starlight
We shine in the dark night
’Cause we are the highlight
We, we’re just living this moment (we are)
Free, on this path that we’ve chosen, oh (free, ah)
We, we’re like diamonds in starlight (we are)
We shine in the dark night
’Cause we are the highlight
Don’t lose your dream, make it reality, baby
Don’t lose your dream, make it
Now everybody let me hear you say
Don’t lose your dream, go and make history, baby
Don’t lose your dream
We, we are breaking through borders
Free, like nobody can stop us, oh
We are diamonds in starlight
’Cause you know that we are
We, we are breaking through borders (we are)
Free, like the clouds are beneath us, oh (free, ah)
We, we’re like diamonds in starlight (we are)
We shine in the dark night
’Cause we are the highlight
We, we’re just living this moment (we are)
Free, on this path that we’ve chosen, oh (free, ah)
We, we’re like diamonds in starlight (we are)
We shine in the dark night
’Cause we are the highlight
turn it up to the top
let’s get it started , go non-stop
Let's get it started, go nonstop
bust through the door , we don’t knock
Bust through the door, we don't knock
( just have a good time )
(Just have a good time)
like we never cared about what they say
tear up the place like it ’s our own
Tear up the place like it's our own
get wilder than a cyclone
and leave it on a high note
and it ’s just like magic lighting up the sky
And it's just like magic lighting up the sky
don’t lose your dream make it reality , baby
Don't lose your dream, make it reality, baby
don’t lose your dream make it
Don't lose your dream, make it
now everybody let me hear you say
oh yeah don’t lose your dream
(Oh yeah!) Don't lose your dream,
go and make history , baby
Go and make history, baby
don’t lose your dream
Don't lose your dream
we are breaking through borders
like the clouds are beneath us , oh
Like the clouds are beneath us, oh
we ’re like diamonds in starlight
We're like diamonds in starlight
we shine in the dark night
‘ cause we are the highlight
'Cause we are the highlight
we are breaking through borders
like the clouds are beneath us , oh
Like the clouds are beneath us, oh
we ’re like diamonds in starlight
We're like diamonds in starlight
we shine in the dark night
‘ cause we are the highlight
'Cause we are the highlight
we are breaking through borders
like the clouds are beneath us , oh
Like the clouds are beneath us, oh
we ’re like diamonds in starlight
We're like diamonds in starlight
Highlight, highlight, highlight, yay!
That was another banger from Kiara,
and I did it with all my beloved ID girls.
I love you, I love you ID girls!
I love you so much! Muah muah muah!
Yes! So after this wonderful banger,
as you may have noticed if you look at the time,
it might be time to end soon, and therefore, I will introduce some merchandise to you guys!
It's birthday merchandise time!
誕生日記念のグッズ出たので紹介したいと思います。どうぞ！
I'd like to introduce my birthday merch. Here you go!
Let's check it out! That is the overview.
And now let me show you all of them in detail.
First of all, the tapestry! Ta-da!
As you can tell, I am in a wedding dress!
なんと、なんと、私、なんかかわいい服着てますね。あー、恥ずかしい！
I'm wearing such a cute outfit... Ah, how embarrassing!
Yeah, um, it's about time, right? I don't know.
It's a beautiful tapestry. I haven't done a tapestry in a while, so I thought you guys deserve one.
It's a beautiful tapestry. I haven't done one in a while, so you guys deserve it.
And next, with the same beautiful face,
and a different expression perhaps, it will be a little badge.
So if you are a badge collector, now's the time... if you haven't eat the bag of chips don't feed to fill up, now's the time to get yourself a Wawa badge, a Wawawaifu badge!
If you're a badge collector, now's the time to get yourself a Wawawaifu badge!
Oh, and by the way, the illustration is by Dotori! Thank you so much, it's so beautiful and looks so cute!
Oh, and by the way, the illustration is by Dotori! Thank you so much, it's so beautiful!
バッチ集めてる人もぜひ今回どうそいっぱい買ってください。ありがとうございます！
If you collect badges, please buy plenty this time! Thank you!
And next up is the lamp! Yeah! The title is 'You Light Up My Life Lamp'!
You, because it's a chicken, it's a KFP chicken!
私の人生を照らしてくれるのがあなたなので、その姿をしたランプでございます！
Because you're the one who lights up my life, it's a lamp shaped like that!
And next we have the Anger Management Frog Ball!
Froggie Wawa! Perfect, right? You want to squeeze and squish her head, don't you? Me too!
ええ、おこて、おこおこマネジメント、ええ、かえるボールでございます！フロギーわわの顔ついているボールです。とてもキュートですけど、
It's the Anger Management Frog Ball! It has Froggie Wawa's face on it. It's super cute, but...
なんか、ね、押したいんだよね、うん！
you kind of want to squish it, yeah!
And next we have a situational voice! Yes! It is matching with the tapestry, actually.
And next we have a situational voice! Yes! It matches with the tapestry, actually.
so it fits it, you know, like, this whole honeymoon wedding situation... just this once, just this once!
So it fits this whole honeymoon wedding situation... just this once!
だけ、
Just...
ええ、ちょっと恥ずかし、ロマンチックなシチュエーションです。
It's a somewhat embarrassing, romantic situational voice pack.
ええ、タペストリーに合わせてます。
It's made to match the tapestry.
日本語もあります。
Japanese is also included.
よかったらどうぞ、キアン！
If you'd like, please check it out, okay?
And for the full set, if you want the full set,
you will get a postcard extra,
and a limited amount will be signed by me with my hand and the rest will be stamped.
で、そのセットを買うと私のサインが入るポストカードが特典になっています。
So, for the set you get, my signature is on the postcard, making it special.
で、そのほかはスタンプです。
And the rest are stamped.
And another special bonus if you get the full set is...
hololive OFFICIAL CARD GAME PR card! "Takanashi Kiara"!
a hololive OFFICIAL CARD GAME PR card! "Takanashi Kiara"!
The purchase of the Birthday Merch Set comes with a bonus card that can be used in the hololive Official Card Game!
But you have to purchase the full set through the official website. GeekJack or any others are not possible.
And if you want to learn how to play, please check out the hololive Official Card Game website! Yay!
タネントプレミアムグッズのフルセット特典としてももう1つ追加、これのカードがついてきます。
Takanento premium goods! The full set also comes with one extra card!
はい、ちゃんとhololive OFFICIAL CARD GAMEで使用できます！
Yay! This can be used in the hololive Official Card Game!
やった！やった、ナイス！特典がたつ。
Yay! That's awesome! Special cards are coming!
And next, after all this merch announcement, let me just tell you that the merch... you can get it after the next song.
Because the next song will be my next original song, and it's called "TASTY"! Ta-da!
Yes, "TASTY" is the name of my next original song, and it will start being released on all streaming services at midnight your time.
Whatever your time zone is, it will be up at midnight.
But the music video will come up right after this, we will raid into it unless it doesn't work.
But we will raid into it, and you will see the music video, and after the music video, the merch will be available at the 10-minute mark of whatever hour you are in, okay?
私的新曲です！やった！「Tasty」でございます！この後披露しますし、この後MVも公開されます！
Watashino shin kyokudesu! Yay! "Tasty" de gozaimasu! Kono ato hiroshimasu shi, kono ato MV mo kōkai saremasu!
で、そのあとにグッズも出ます！よろしくお願いします！
De, sono atoniグッズも出ます！Yoroshiku onegaishimasu!
よろしくお願いします！Yay!
Yoroshiku onegaishimasu! Yay!
So, with that, it is finally time for the last song of my birthday live and my new original song.
So please listen to "TASTY".
Tongue tied, oh you don’t gotta hide it
Obvious I get you excited
Don’t want perfume on my skin
Just need you, yeah
Sugary thoughts, nah I don’t mind it
Confection affection, it feels right
Flavor makes you go
No beggin’ needed, just take a bite
Lemme show you what I can take, make ache
I’ll make you feel like you’re alive
Alive
Feel your heartbeat
Honey drippin, you see
What we’ve done tonight
Just a little taste of me
Sweet like sugar, rotten down to the core
Savor every little taste
Give you more
Flavored hard candy
Addictive, so sweet
You got me like that
That that that that
T-taste me
Gettin’ every drop
You know you like it a lot
You know I’m taste-taste-taste-tasty
Taste me
Tell me what do you want
I’ll be your la-lollipop
You know I’m taste-taste-taste-tasty
Baby look at my picture
Know you wanna be my mister, mister
I can be a little bitter, switch up, whimper, worship me like I’m scripture
This sickly sweet
Candied love
Makes you want more, mm wow
Are you satisfied now?
Hear you say
You want me
Can’t stop the way your eyes wander, oh
So dolce
Lemme show you what I can take, make ache
I’ll make you feel like you’re alive
Alive
Feel your heartbeat
Honey drippin, you see
What we’ve done tonight
Just a little taste of me
Sweet like sugar, rotten down to the core
Savor every little taste
Give you more
Flavored hard candy
Addictive, so sweet
That that that that
Ooh
Sweet aroma
Got us both actin' up tonight
tonight
Ooh
Sugar coma
Fall into me know you want it
Ooh
Baby, i'm sweet for you
I'ma keep it tasty, tasty
Know you like this taste, taste, taste
T-taste me
Gettin' every drop
You know you like it a lot
You know I'm taste-taste-taste-tasty
Taste me
Tell me what do you want
I'll be your la-lollipop
You know I'm taste-taste-taste-tasty
So sweet, not enough of me
Drippin' sugary, just for you
taste, taste, taste, taste
So sweet, got a crush on me
Sugar rush right into you
taste, taste, taste, taste
Not enough of me Drippin -
Not enough of me, drippin'...
taste, taste, taste, taste
So sweet, got a crush on me Sugar rush